mastermindpros.com 2008-09-11

# Mastermind Pros - Privacy Policy

### WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY

The Internet is an amazing tool. It has the power to change the way we live, and we're starting to see that potential today. With only a few mouse-clicks, you can follow the news, look up facts, buy goods and services, and communicate with others from around the world. It's important to MastermindPros.com (Cash Mastermind Team 1 LLC) to help our customers retain their privacy when they take advantage of all the Internet has to offer.

We believe your business is no one else's. Your privacy is important to you and to us. So we'll protect the information you share with us. To protect your privacy, MastermindPros.com (Cash Mastermind Team 1 LLC) follow different principles in accordance with worldwide practices for customer privacy and data protection.

  * We won’t sell or give away your name, mail address, phone number, email address or any other information to anyone. 
  * We’ll use state-of-the-art security measures to protect your information from unauthorized users. 

### NOTICE

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you create your membership and/or subscribe to member updates or other in house mail. We use your Personal Information for four primary purposes:

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once. 
  * To help you quickly find software, services or information. 
  * To help us create content most relevant to you. 
  * To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from MastermindPros.com (Cash Mastermind Team 1 LLC). 

### CONSENT

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you cannot access the member area.

If you decide to register, you will be able to select the kinds of information you want to receive from us by subscribing to various services, like our member update or special offers. If you do not want us to communicate with you about other offers regarding MastermindPros.com (Cash Mastermind Team 1 LLC) products, programs, events, or services by email, postal mail, or telephone, you may select the option stating that you do not wish to receive marketing messages from MastermindPros.com (Cash Mastermind Team 1 LLC). 

### ACCESS

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time from your member profile. There, you can:

  * View and edit personal information you have already given us. 
  * Tell us whether you want us to send you member updates or special offers. 

### SECURITY

MastermindPros.com (Cash Mastermind Team 1 LLC) has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

We guarantee your transactions to be 100% safe and secure. When you place orders or access your personal affiliate account information, you're utilizing secure server software SSL, which encrypts your personal information before it's sent over the Internet. SSL is one of the safest encryption technologies available.

In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

MastermindPros.com (Cash Mastermind Team 1 LLC) strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in the 

USA or any other country where MastermindPros.com (Cash Mastermind Team 1 LLC), its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can share these see or edit your personal information without knowing your user name and password, so do not with others.

### NOTICE TO PARENTS

We adhere to the Children's Privacy Act. You must be 18 years of age to join or use MastermindPros.com (Cash Mastermind Team 1 LLC) or any of the recommended or linked sites. This site follows the guidelines, policies and laws of the Federal Trade Commission (www.ftc.gov). We retain the right to refuse anyone membership in any of our sites.

### ENFORCEMENT

If for some reason you believe MastermindPros.com (Cash Mastermind Team 1 LLC) has not adhered to these principles, please notify us, and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line.

### ELECTRONIC PRODUCT REGISTRATION

When you buy and install a new product, we may ask you to register your purchase electronically. When you do, we merge your registration information with any information you've already left with us (we call that information your personal profile). If you haven't previously registered with us, we create a personal profile for you from your product registration information. If you ever want to review or update that information, you can click on Update Profile, and edit any of the Personal Information in your profile. If you haven't already created a membership, we will ask you to do so. This ensures that only you can access your information.

### CUSTOMER PROFILES

As mentioned above, every registered customer has a unique personal profile. Each profile is assigned a unique personal identification username, which helps us ensure that only you can access your profile.

When you register, you create your profile, your username and password. It is your passport to seamless travel across your member area, allowing you to download software and order more plugin modules without having to fill out registration forms with information you've already provided. Even if you switch computers, you won't have to re-register – just use your Registration ID to identify yourself.

### WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION YOU SHARE

When you join us, you provide us with your contact information, including your name and email address. We use this information to send you updates about your order, questionnaires to measure your satisfaction with our service and announcements about new and exciting services that we offer. When you order from us, our 3rd party payment processors such as paypal and 2checkout will ask for your credit card number and billing address. They use this information only to bill you for the product(s) you order at that time.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including programming,  answering customer questions about products or services, sending email and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

MastermindPros.com (Cash Mastermind Team 1 LLC) will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on MastermindPros.com (Cash Mastermind Team 1 LLC) or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of MastermindPros.com (Cash Mastermind Team 1 LLC) and its family of Websites, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of MastermindPros.com (Cash Mastermind Team 1 LLC), its Websites, or the public.
